Grove Press Records
Grove Press Records
- Books - Book files (by author)
  - Brecht, Bertolt
    - The Caucasian Chalk Circle
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1977-1978 (Box 151)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 151)
      - Publicity, 1961; 1965-1967 (Box 151)
      - Rights and permissions, 1965; 1969 (Box 151)
    - Edward II
      - Correspondence, 1963; 1966,; 1968-1969; includes errata (Box 151)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 151)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 151)
      - Publicity, 1966 (Box 151)
      - Rights and permissions, 1967 (Box 151)
    - The Exception and the Rule
      - Contract, Bentley, 1964 (Box 151)
      - Rights and permissions, 1965; 1967,; 1972 (Box 151)
    - Galileo
      - Copyright, 1960; 1966 (Box 151)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1976-1980 (Box 151)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 151)
      - Publicity, 1966-1967; 1971,; 1975 (Box 152)
      - Rights and permissions, 1963-1964; 1968-1969,; 1971-1973 (Box 152)
    - The Good Woman of Setzuan
      - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 152)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1976-1978 (Box 152)
      - Rights and permissions, 1968-1969 (Box 152)
    - Happy End
      - Correspondence, 1963-1965; 1970 (Box 152)
      - Script, 1964; includes letter from Leo Kerr (Box 152)
    - The Jewish Wife and Other Short Plays
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1976-1978 (Box 152)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 152)
      - Publicity, 1965; 1969 (Box 152)
      - Rights and permissions, 1967-1969; 1972 (Box 152)
    - Jungle of Cities and Other Plays
      - Correspondence, Gerhard Nellhaus, 1961-1964; claiming authorship of Bentley's translation (Box 152)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 152)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 152)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1961; 1964-1965,; undated; includes Frank Jones, Eric Bentley, Anselm Hollo (translators) (Box 152)
    - Kalendergeschichten
      - Correspondence, 1961; 1963 (Box 152)
    - Lehrstücke [The Didactic Plays of Bertolt Brecht]
      - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 152)
    - Mahagonny
      - Project file, 1965-1967; includes photocopy of a bilingual (English and German) printed version of the script (Box 152)
    - A Man's a Man
      - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 152)
      - Publicity, 1962 (Box 152)
    - Manual of Piety
      - Correspondence, 1966-1972; Professor Hugo Schmidt, Lotte Lenya (photocopy), others (Box 152)
      - Production, Camera copy, bilingual edition (Box 153)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1973-1974 (Box 153)
      - Production, Photograph, 1966 (Box 153)
      - Production, Setting copy (incomplete), 2 folders (Box 153)
      - Production, Setting copy, 3 folders (Box 153)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1966-1967 (Box 153)
      - Publicity, General, 1966-1968; 1977; 2 folders (Box 154)
    - The Measures Taken
      - Publicity, 1974 (Box 154)
    - The Mother
      - Correspondence, 1967-1968; 1970,; 1974; includes copyright (Box 154)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1963; 1965,; 1968; includes photographs (Box 154)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 154)
      - Publicity, 1965-1966 (Box 154)
      - Rights and permissions, 1969 (Box 154)
    - Mother Courage and Her Children
      - Correspondence, photographs, 1973; with Bentley, regarding brochure (Box 154)
      - Photographs by Martha Holmes (Box 154)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1977-1980 (Box 154)
      - Production, Proofs, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Project file, 1959; 1961-1963; correspondence, corrections, page proofs for book of songs, etc. (Box 154)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1962; 1966 (Box 154)
      - Publicity, General, 1962-1966 (Box 154)
      - Rights and permissions, 1963-1972 (Box 155)
      - Royalties, Bentley (E-372), 1963-1969 (Box 155)
    - Parables for the Theatre
      - Correspondence, 1963-1965; University of Minnesota Press, Bentley (Box 155)
      - Production, Proofs (F&Gs) (Box 155)
      - Production, Setting copy, disbound University of Minnesota hardcover edition; 2 folders (Box 155)
      - Production, Text copy, 1961 (Box 155)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1965; 1967 (Box 155)
      - Royalties, University of Minnesota Press (GP-174), 1962-1968 (Box 155)
      - Royalties, University of Minnesota Press (E-53), 1956-1968 (Box 155)
    - Schweyk
      - Correspondence, Dorothy Kreymborg (translator), 1960; 1964 (Box 155)
    - Selected Poems
      - Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 155)
      - Production, Camera copy, disbound Reynal and Hitchcock hardcover edition (Box 155)
      - Publicity, 1965-1966 (Box 156)
    - Seven Plays
      - Production, Photograph (Box 156)
      - Project file, 1960-1961; 1964; correspondence, editor's notes, etc. (Box 156)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1960-1961; includes Arthur Schlesinger Jr. letter (Box 156)
      - Publicity, General, 1961-1962 (Box 156)
      - Rights and permissions, 1962; 1966,; 1969-1970 (Box 156)
    - Theaterarbeit
      - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 156)
    - Threepenny Novel
      - Correspondence and contracts, 1956; 1959,; 1974 (Box 156)
      - Royalties, Robert Hale, Ltd. (E-42), 1956-1968 (Box 156)
      - Royalties, Stefan Brecht (E-42), 1959-1969; includes letter from Stefan Brecht (Box 156)
    - Threepenny Opera
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1968; 1977-1978,; 1980 (Box 156)
      - Publicity, 1960 (Box 156)
      - Rights and permissions, 1970 (Box 156)
    - Visions of Simone Marchard
      - Correspondence, Marta Feuchtwanger, 1963-1964 (Box 156)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 156)
    - [unidentified play]
      - Royalties, Gerhard Nellhaus (translator), 1962-1971; includes contract (Box 150)
  - Bree, Germaine
    - Marcel Proust & Deliverance from Time
      - Contract, Rutgers University Press, 1958 (Box 156)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1958; includes postcard from author (Box 156)
      - Royalties, Rutgers University Press (E-123), 1958-1966 (Box 156)
  - Bregeon, Janine
    - A Useless Day [Un Journee Inutile]
      - Correspondence, Author, 1969 (Box 156)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 156)
      - Photograph, Author (Box 156)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 156)
      - Project file, 1966-1968; cover, reader's report, notes (Box 156)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1968 (Box 156)
      - Publicity, General, 1968-1968 (Box 156)
  - Breisach, Ernst
    - Introduction to Modern Existentialism
      - Correspondence, Author, 1960-1963; 1970; also mentions his Europe in the Age of the Italian Renaissance (Box 156)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1963; 1966,; 1971-1972 (Box 156)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1962-1971; 1977; 2 folders (Box 157)
      - Project file, 1960-1963; copyright, editorial notes, press release, etc. (Box 157)
      - Royalties (GP-265), 1961-1964 (Box 157)
  - Breitman, George, See under X, Malcolm.
  - Brenan, Gerald
    - The Face of Spain
      - Contract, Farrar Straus & Cudahy, 1956 (Box 157)
      - Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 157)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1959 (Box 157)
      - Publicity, 1956-1958 (Box 157)
      - Royalties, Farrar Straus & Cudahy (E-51), 1956-1960 (Box 157)
    - South from Granada
      - Contract, Farrar Straus & Cudahy, 1957 (Box 157)
      - Correspondence, 1957; 1961; includes cover from FS&C edition, article by Brennan clipped from The Atlantic (Box 157)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1957-1958 (Box 157)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1957-1959 (Box 157)
      - Royalties, Farrar Straus & Cudahy (E-115), 1958-1963 (Box 157)
  - Brennan, Garnet E.
    - Correspondence, Author, 1967-1968 (Box 157)
  - Brenton, Howard
    - Weapons of Happiness
      - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 157)
  - Bresson, Robert
    - A Man Escaped
      - Correspondence, Author, 1968 (Box 157)
  - Breton, Andre
    - Manifestoes of Surrealism, See Correspondence-Subject files: Seaver.
    - Nadja
      - Correspondence, 1960-1961; 1964-1968 (Box 157)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1960-1961; 1964,; 1977-1978 (Box 157)
      - Production, Page repros, pp. 1-119; 3 folders (Box 157)
      - Production, Page repros, pp. 120-190 (Box 158)
    - Surrealism and Painting
      - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 158)
  - de la Bretonne, Restif
    - Monsieur Nicolas
      - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 158)
  - Briggs, William A.
    - Correspondence, Author, 1959-1965 (Box 158)
    - Anthology of Zen
      - Contract, Briggs, 1960 (Box 158)
      - Contract, University Microfilms, 1969-1970 (Box 158)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1964; 1971 (Box 158)
      - Project file, 1960-1961; copyright, proposal, editor's notes, acknowledgements, etc. (Box 158)
      - Publicity, 1960-1962 (Box 158)
      - Royalties, Briggs (E-289), 1961-1965; 1974 (Box 158)
  - Brightman, Carol
    - Vietnam, See McDermott, John: Vietnam.
  - Brim, John A.
    - Chinese Sex
      - Correspondence, Author, 1972-1973 (Box 158)
      - Production, Manuscript, pages 1-38 (Box 158)
  - Brinnin, John Malcolm
    - The Third Rose
      - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 158)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1960-1961 (Box 158)
      - Publicity, 1959-1961 (Box 158)
      - Royalties, Little, Brown & Company (E-278), 1960-1963 (Box 158)
  - Brissette, Gerard G.
    - The Lesbian Way of Life [alternate title: The Lesbian Handbook], alternate title: The Lesbian Handbook
      - Contract, 1969 (Box 158)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1969-1971 (Box 158)
      - Correspondence, 1969; 1971 (Box 158)
      - Royalties, 1969-1971; mentions Maria Louis Porter as author of this book (Box 158)
  - Bronsteen, Ruth [later Ruth Harris]
    - The Making of Mayor O'Stremsky
      - Contract, 1970 (Box 158)
      - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 158)
      - Royalties, Harold Matson, 1970-1971 (Box 158)
  - Broonzy, William and Yannick Bruynoghe
    - Big Bill Blues
      - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 158)
      - Correspondence, Authors, 1956; 1960-1961,; 1963 (Box 158)
      - Photographs, Authors, 1956 (Box 158)
      - Project file, 1956-1957; production estimate, reader's report (Box 158)
      - Publicity, 1956-1959 (Box 158)
  - Broughton, James
    - Correspondence, Author, 1955-1962; 1968-1969,; undated (Box 158)
    - Photograph, Author (Box 159)
    - An Almanac for Amorists
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1955-1956 (Box 159)
      - Royalties (GP-71), 1955-1957; 1959,; 1969 (Box 159)
    - Musical Chairs
      - Production, Jacket proofs (Box 159)
      - Royalties (GP-72), 1955-1957 (Box 159)
    - The Playground
      - Royalties (HB-119), 1957; 1969 (Box 159)
    - True and False Unicorn
      - Contract, 1956 (Box 159)
      - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 159)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1957-1960 (Box 159)
      - Royalties (E-75, HB-118-118A), 1957-1961 (Box 159)
  - Brown, Deena
    - American Yoga
      - Contract, 1979 (Box 159)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1979-1981 (Box 159)
      - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 159)
      - Production, Galleys, 2 folders (Box 159)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1979-1981 (Box 159)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 159)
      - Project file, 1978-1979; reader's report, table of contents, editorial notes, etc. (Box 160)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1981 (Box 160)
  - Brown, Lennox
    - Devil Mas
      - Correspondence, author and others, 1974-1978; includes mention of several other works (Box 160)
  - Brown, Turner, Jr.
    - Black Is
      - Contract, 1968 (Box 160)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 160)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1968-1969 (Box 160)
      - Production, Mechanicals, 2 folders (Box 160)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 160)
      - Rights and permissions, 1969-1973 (Box 160)
      - Royalties, Sterling Lord (B-203), 1969-1973 (Box 160)
  - Browning, Bart
    - Sex Illustrator
      - Project file, 1972-1973; contract, correspondence (Box 160)
    - The Uncontrollable Muscle
      - Project file, 1972; contract, correspondence (Box 160)
  - Bruckner, Pascal
    - Evil Angels: A Novel
      - Correspondence, Author, 1986; Spanish title: Lunes de Fiel (Box 160)
      - Production, Manuscript, copyedited; 2 folders (Box 160)
      - Project file, 1986 (Box 160)
  - Brusell, James A.
    - Casebook of a Crime Psychologist
      - Project file, 1968; introduction by Gerald Frank; Brussel's c.v.; editorial fact sheet; jacket for GP-532 edition (Box 160)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1968 (Box 160)
  - Brusendorff, Ove
    - Seksual Leksikon, See Moller, J. Fabricius: Seksual Leksikon.
  - Buck, Pearl S.
    - All Men Are Brothers
      - Contract, John Day and Company, 1957 (Box 160)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1964; includes covers of Hitchcock and Grove editions (Box 160)
      - Publicity (Box 161)
      - Royalties, John Day and Company (HB-117), 1957-1964 (Box 161)
  - Buckley, Bill
    - Arkansas Jail
      - Correspondence, Author, 1968 (Box 161)
      - Project file, 1968; photographs, clippings related to the case, longish typescript summarizing the case (Box 161)
  - Buitrago, Ann Mari and Leon Andrew Immerman
    - Are You Now or Have You Ever Been in the F.B.I. Files?
      - Production, Draft manuscript, 3 folders (Box 161)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1979-1981 (Box 161)
      - Production, Manuscript, "material to be added to manuscript" (Box 161)
      - Production, Manuscript, partial (photocopy) (Box 161)
      - Production, Original manuscript, 3 folders (Box 161)
      - Production, Original manuscript, "deleted materials" (Box 161)
      - Production, Page proofs, multiple sets, including repros; 13 folders (Box 162)
      - Production, Page proofs (Box 163)
  - Bulatovic, Miodrag
    - Contract, Bernard Geis, 1960; Devils Are Coming; The Red Cock Flies to Heaven; The Wolf and the Bell (Box 163)
    - Correspondence, Author, 1960; 1965-1966 (Box 163)
    - Royalties, Bernard Geis, 1961; 1963-1964; Devils Are Coming; The Red Cock Flies to Heaven; The Wolf and the Bell (Box 163)
    - Godot Has Arrived
      - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 163)
      - Production, Manuscript, typescript of introduction and post-script, in French (Box 163)
      - Publicity, 1966; includes "Excerpt from interview between Bulatovic and Bienek" typescript with corrections (Box 163)
    - The Lovers
      - Production, Manuscript, chapter 1 only (Box 163)
    - The Red Cock Flies to Heaven
      - Production, Camera copy, in German (Box 163)
      - Production, Manuscript, chapter 1 only (Box 163)
      - Production, Page proofs, 4 folders (Box 163)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1962 (Box 163)
    - The Wolf and the Bell
      - Correspondence, 1960; 1965; includes typesript of essay, "Yugoslav critics on Miodrag Bulatovic's book The Wolf and the Bell" by Z. Milic (Box 163)
      - Publicity, 1958 (Box 163)
  - Bulgakov, Mikhail
    - Correspondence, general, 1967; 1969 (Box 163)
    - Photographs, author (Box 163)
    - Bliss
      - Contract, Mirra Ginsburg (translator) (Box 163)
      - Correspondence, Mirra Ginsburg (translator), 1969-1970 (Box 164)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 164)
      - Royalties, Gunther Stuhlman, 1968-1969 (Box 164)
    - Flight
      - Correspondence, Mirra Ginsburg (translator), 1968-1970 (Box 164)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 164)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 164)
      - Project file, 1969; cover, summary by Ginsburg, production/design notes (Box 164)
      - Publicity, Grove (Box 164)
      - Publicity, General, 1969-1970 (Box 164)
    - The Heart of a Dog
      - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 164)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 164)
      - Project file, 1968; production notes, reader's reports, etc. (Box 164)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1968; 1971; includes jackets for both editions (B-193 and GP-313) (Box 164)
      - Publicity, General, 1968 (Box 164)
    - The Master and Margarita
      - Contract, Mirra Ginsburg (translator), 1967 (Box 164)
      - Correspondence, Mirra Ginsburg (translator), 1967-1968; 1978 (Box 164)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 164)
      - Production, Corrections (Box 165)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1970; 1978,; 1980 (Box 165)
      - Production, Manuscript, preface, translator's note by Ginsburg, chapter 2, afterword by A. Vulis; 4 folders (Box 165)
      - Production, Setting copy, 6 folders (Box 165)
      - Project file, 1967; 1977; biographical information on Bulgakov and Ginsburg, reader's reports, notes on reprinting, misc. notes (Box 165)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1967-1969; includes jackets for both Grove editions (B-147, GP-433) and the Harper & Row edition (Box 165)
      - Publicity, General, 1967-1969; 4 folders (Box 166)
      - Royalties, Gunther Stuhlman / Mirra Ginsburg (GP-433) 1967-1970 (Box 166)
      - Royalties, Selig O. Wassner (GP-433), 1967-1970 (Box 166)
    - Teatro
      - Reader's report, 1968 (Box 166)
  - Bullins, Ed
    - [Various titles], The Duplex; Pigpen plus three short plays; Short Stories; Ten Short Plays
      - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 166)
      - Correspondence, author, 1967; 1970 (Box 166)
      - Project file, contract notes, recommendations by John Lahr; circa 1969 (Box 166)
  - Bullock, Paul
    - Watts: The Aftermath
      - Contract, 1968 (Box 166)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1968-1970 (Box 166)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 166)
      - Production, Revised repros, 2 folders (Box 166)
      - Production, Revised repros, 8 folders (Box 167)
      - Production, Setting copy, pp. 1-84 (Box 167)
      - Production, Setting copy, pp. 85-378; 4 folders (Box 168)
      - Project file, 1970 (Box 168)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1969-1970; includes jackets for both editions (GP-562, B-242) (Box 168)
      - Publicity, General, 1969-1970 (Box 168)
  - Bunuel, Luis
    - [various titles], L'Age D'Or, Nazarin, Un Chien Andalou
      - Contract, 1968 (Box 168)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1968 (Box 168)
  - Del Buono, Oreste
    - Correspondence, general, 1963-1966 (Box 168)
    - Photographs, Author (Box 168)
    - Image of Love
      - Contract, copyright, 1960; 1990 (Box 168)
      - Correspondence, 1959-1964; includes carbon of letter to author (Box 168)
      - Production, Page repros, 3 folders (Box 169)
      - Project file, 1961-1963; proposal, reader's reports, production estimates, etc. (Box 169)
      - Publicity, 1959; 1962-1963 (Box 169)
      - Royalties, Fabio Coen / Feltrinelli (HB-282), 1960-1967 (Box 169)
  - Burroughs, William S.
    - "Battle of Chicago: From the Yippies Side", 1968; long article from New York Times regarding the Democractic National Convention in Chicago and the involvement of the "yippies" (Box 169)
    - Bibliography project, Joe Maynard, 1972-1976; correspondence with Maynard, lists, etc. (Box 169)
    - "Conversation on sequence of Burroughs' books", 1980; Allen Ginsberg interview; includes transcript with photocopy of letter (Box 169)
    - Correspondence, Author, 1960-1972; 2 folders (Box 169)
    - Correspondence, general, 1969-1970; 1975-1977 (Box 170)
    - Rights and permissions, general, 1967-1973 (Box 170)
    - Call Me Burroughs
      - Recording, Realisation S.F.P.P., Paris, France, Apr 1965; grove_071; excerpts from Naked Lunch and Nova Express, read by William Burroughs; 1 phonodisc, 33-1/3 rpm
    - Dutch Schultz
      - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 170)
    - The Job, with Daniel Odier
      - Contract, 1969 (Box 170)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 170)
      - Photo, author, undated (Box 170)
      - Production, galleys, undated; three sets (A, B, C); 7 folders (Box 170)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1970; 1974,; 1980; 3 folders (Box 170)
      - Production, manuscript, 1968; 1974; 2 folders (Box 170)
      - Production, manuscript, 1968 (Box 171)
      - Production, setting copy, 1969 (Box 171)
      - Publicity, 1970 (Box 171)
    - Junkie
      - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 171)
    - Naked Lunch
      See also Call Me Burroughs, above.
      - Contracts, other publishers, 1960; 1962,; 1965,; 1969 (Box 171)
      - Comments on, 1960-1961; Miller, Ferlinghetti (Box 171)
      - Legal, Massachusetts v. Naked Lunch, 1962-1965; correspondence (Box 171)
      - Legal, Massachusetts v. Naked Lunch, 1959; Lady Chatterley hearing (photocopy) (Box 171)
      - Legal, Massachusetts v. Naked Lunch, 1965; trial transcripts; 3 folders (Box 171)
      - Legal, Massachusetts v. Naked Lunch, 1965; trial transcripts (Box 172)
      - Legal, Mavrikos case, 1963 (Box 172)
      - Legal, Olympia Press v. Grove, 1967 (Box 172)
      - Legal, Publicity, 1962-1966; includes letter to Girodias about first arest related to Naked Lunch (Box 172)
      - Legal, U.S. Customs seizure, 1960 (Box 172)
      - Production, Camera copy, 1959; 5 folders (Box 172)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1966; material for introduction (Box 172)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1966 (Box 172)
      - Production, manuscript, undated; 2 folders (Box 172)
      - Production, setting copy, undated (Box 172)
      - Project file, 1959-1961 (Box 172)
      - Project file, 1960-1962; Girodias' comments on Putnam's refusal to pay out owed royalties; Halliday Lithograph's refusal to print (Box 173)
      - Project file, 1961-1965 (Box 173)
      - Project file, 1961-1980 (Box 173)
      - Project file, 1962 (Box 173)
      - Project file, 1963-1966 (Box 173)
      - Project file, 1968-1975 (Box 173)
      - Project file, 1972 (Box 173)
      - Project file, 1984 (Box 173)
      - Project file, undated (Box 173)
      - Publicity, 1952-1967; 4 folders (Box 173)
      - Publicity, 1962-1975; 7 folders (Box 174)
      - Publicity, Photographs (Box 174)
      - Rights and permissions, 1959-1973; 2 folders (Box 174)
      - Royalties, Harold Matson (GP-596), 1971-1973 (Box 175)
    - Nova Express
      - Contracts, 1961; 1965-1966 (Box 175)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1966; 1969 (Box 175)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1966 (Box 175)
      - Project files, 1962-1969; 3 folders (Box 175)
      - Publicity, Grove (Box 175)
      - Publicity, General, 1962-1965 (Box 175)
    - Right Where You Are Sitting Now
      - Contracts, 1965 (Box 175)
      - Royalties, Harold Matson, 1965-1971 (Box 175)
    - The Soft Machine
      - Contract, 1965; 2 folders (Box 175)
      - Correspondence, 1963; 1965-1966 (Box 175)
      - Cover art, 1966; original ink-on-paper; photographs (Box 175)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1966; 1977 (Box 175)
      - Production, setting copy, undated (Box 175)
      - Project file, 1962-1968 (Box 175)
      - Publicity, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 176)
    - The Third Mind, with Brion Gysin
      - Correspondence, Gysin, 1970; includes photo (Box 176)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1970; most with Peter Matson (Box 176)
      - "Original material", undated (Box 176)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1968-1971; 2 folders (Box 176)
      - Project file, 1968-1971 (Box 176)
    - Three Novels: The Soft Machine, Nova Express and Wild Boys
      - Production, Camera copy, 1980; 2 folders (Box 176)
      - Production, Camera copy, 1980; 2 folders (Box 177)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1967; 1981; 2 folders (Box 177)
    - The Ticket That Exploded
      - Contract, 1965-1968 (Box 177)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 177)
      - Photo, author, 1967 (Box 177)
      - Production, Camera copy, undated (Box 177)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 177)
      - Production, setting copy, 1966; 3 folders (Box 177)
      - Project file, 1966-1969 (Box 177)
      - Publicity, Grove (Box 177)
      - Publicity, General, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 177)
    - Wild Boys
      - Correspondence, 1971-1973; topics of discussion include royalty and contract issues, litigation over rights to Wild Boys and other Burroughs books, Grove's overall relationship with Burroughs (Box 178)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1971 (Box 178)